(Sheldon:)You're right. I'm smart as a whip.
l should be able to figure this out.
(Leonard:)Listen, I kind of made plans
with the guys this weekend.
l wondered, because
we're in this relationship beta test...
(Leonard:)...if I should have asked you first.
(Leonard:)Then I thought if
l did check with you first...
(Leonard:)...you'd think that
l was taking things too seriously...
...and then I got a nosebleed.
(Penny:)You don't have to check with me.
Do whatever you want.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Guess I was hoping
for a different reaction, but okay.
- Really? What were you hoping for?
- l don't know.
(Leonard:)Maybe that you'd be a little upset.
(Leonard:)And then you'd realize that
I'm a stallion that has to run free.
(Leonard:)And that would turn you on a little.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm an actress. Ask me again.
(Leonard:)Do you mind if I spend the weekend
playing games with the guys?